We're picking peaches now.
A peach should smell very good first and foremost, it should have a nice fruity smell to it.
If it doesn't have a fruity smell it's not ripe, so make sure you pick it up and smell it.
You want to get your peach and pick it and you want to feel your peach.
You want to feel your peach and make sure that it has a nice slight pressure like this one does, you don't want to push it too hard though you don't want to bruise your peach guys, be very gentle with the peach.
You want to make sure there's no discoloration of the peach, you don't want to see any really, really dark moldy looking spots, you want it to be nice and clean like this one.
Feel it again, make sure it's nice all the way around and you should have good peaches all the time.
You want to store your peach outside of the refrigerator, not in the refrigerator.
A lot of people make that mistake.
So first and foremost; smell nice and fruity, feel nice and tender and you want to make sure there's no discoloration of any kind.
You guys will have good peaches every time single times if you follow these simple, simple steps guys and make sure not to store in the refrigerator again, okay.
Another thing I want to tell you actually is if you live somewhere that grows produce, you want to definitely buy from a local grower rather than buying from a big chain store.
A lot of times these big chain stores just want to get their produce in and out and sell them as quick as possible so they're going to buy the produced unripe and they're going to hope they ripe on the way to the store and that's what they do.
So these local farmers usually don't put their produce until it's nice and ripe, so look out for that guys.
Thank you and have a good day.